<resources>

    <string name="app_name">UCG-2017</string>



    <string-array name="list1">
        <item>te</item>
        <item>te</item>
        <item>te</item>
        <item>te</item>
        <item>te</item>
        <item>te</item>
        <item>te</item>
        <item>te</item>
        <item>te</item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="guest_name">
        <item>Dr. Kirit S Parikh </item>
        <item>Dr. Pradeep K Singh </item>
        <item>Dr. Michael S Blinderman </item>
        <item>Prof. Amit Garg </item>
        <item>Prof. Sanjay M Mahajani </item>
        <item>Prof. T Sundararajan </item>
        <item>Prof. Anand B Rao</item>
        <item>Dr. Dipankar Chatterjee</item>
        <item>Dr. Ajay K Singh </item>
        <item>Dr. Debadutta Mohanty </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="guest_details">
        <item>Dr Kirit S Parikh has a Doctor of Science in Civil Engineering and a Masters Degree in Economics from MIT, USA.\n

Dr. Parikh is a Former Member of the Planning Commission of the Government of India and is currently the Chairman of the Integrated Research and Action for Development (IRADe), New Delhi. He also was the Founder Director of the Indira Gandhi Institute of Development Research (IGIDR), Mumbai.

\nHe was the Chairman of the Integrated Energy Policy Committee, Planning Commission. He was a Member of the Economic Advisory Council (EAC) of the Prime Ministers of India, Atal Behari Vajpayee, P.V. Narasimha Rao, Chandra Shekhar, V.P.Singh and Rajiv Gandhi. In the past he had also been a member of the National Committee for Environmental Planning and Co-ordination, the National Committee on Science and Technology and the Fuel Policy Committee.

\nHe was honored with the Padma Bhushan which is the third highest civilian honor conferred by the President of India. He is a Fellow of the National Academy of Sciences, India. He was honoured as the most distinguished and illustrious alumni of the decade from India by the Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT), USA in September, 2007. He was conferred the Distinguished Alumnus Award by Indian Institute of Technology (IIT), Kharagpur in September, 2007. He was felicitated as one of the engineering personalities by the Indian Engineering Congress, December 2006.

\nDr. Parikh had been the editor of "India Development Report" which provides a non-governmental assessment of India100s development and policy options.
</item>
        <item>
            Dr. Pradeep Kumar Singh, Director, CSIR-CIMFR, holds a doctoral degree from tRRhe Technical University, Clausthal, Germany. Dr. Singh has made notable contributions in Explosives Science and Blasting Technologies to solve practical problems in the mining industry encompassing the fields of optimal use of explosives energy in rock fragmentation, explosives energy partitioning, blast vibrations, wall-control, fragmentation control, blast design in mines and tunnels, pre-split blast design, cast blast designs in coal mining operations besides correlating structural damage due to blast vibrations. Dr. Singh has authored 274 technical reports sponsored by different organizations and 9 SandT reports funded by Ministry of Coal, Government of India. There are 114 published papers in referred National and International Journals/Symposia to his credit. He is also the author of 3 books. Dr. Singh is recipient of prestigious National Mineral Award by the Ministry of Mines, Government of India. He is Chairman of International Committee on Rock Fragmentation by Blasting, Headquarters in Spain; Representing India in the International Committee on World Forum of University on Resources and Sustainability, Headquarters in Germany.
        </item>
        <item>
            Dr. Michael S Blinderman is Director (Operations) at Ergo Exergy Inc, Montreal, Canada. He has more than 30 years of experience in commercial development of Underground Coal Gasification. He co-founded Laurus Energy Inc in 2007.
        </item>
        <item>

Prof. Amit Garg is a Professor in the Public Systems Group, Indian Institute of Management Ahmedabad. He is currently the Chairman of the Doctoral Programme at IIM Ahmedabad. An alumnus of IIT Roorkee and IIM Ahmedabad, Prof. Garg has previously been Senior Economist at the UNEP Risoe Centre, Technical University of Denmark (DTU), Denmark and also an executive with the Indian Railway Service of Signal Engineers (IRSSE).

\nHe is the recipient of the IIMA Outstanding Researcher Award 2016 and the IIMA Distinguished Young Professor Award for Excellence in Research 2010. He was awarded by the Hon100ble Prime Minister of India for his contribution to the Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change (IPCC).

\nProf. Garg has been involved in several international research exercises including the UNEP Emissions
            Gap Report, the IPCC Emission Factor Database, lead author of three IPCC reports,lead reviewer for UN Framework Convention on Climate Change and so on. He has also advised several Indian government departments on climate change related issues.

\nHe has co-authored six books, nineteen international research reports, thirteen book chapters and forty peer-reviewed journal articles.


        </item>
        <item>
            Prof. Sanjay M Mahajani is a Professor of Chemical Engineering at the Indian Institute of Technology Bombay. He holds a PhD from the University of Bombay. His areas of interest include Reaction Engineering and Catalysis, Process Intensification and Coal and Biomass Gasification. Prof. Mahajani has received several awards for his teaching at IIT Bombay. He has authored more than 100 peer-reviewed journal articles and has two patents to his credit.

        </item>
        <item>
            Prof. T Sundararajan is a Professor at the Indian Institute of Technology Madras. He headed the Department of Mechanical Engineering at IIT Madras. Previously, he was a faculty member at IIT Kanpur. He holds a Bachelors degree from IIT Madras and a doctorate from the University of Pennsylvania. Prof. Sundararajan has guided several doctoral students and managed several RandD and consultancy projects. He has authored more than a 100 peer-reviewed journal articles. Prof. Sundararajan is a Fellow of the Indian National Academy of Engineering.

        </item>
        <item>

Prof. Anand B Rao is an Associate Professor at the Indian Institute of Technology Bombay. He teaches courses at CTARA, Department of Energy Science and Engineering and IDP in Climate Studies. He is guiding several doctoral and masters students. Prof. Rao holds Bachelor and Masters degrees from IIT Bombay and a doctoral degree in Engineering and Public Policy from the Carnegie Mellon University, USA. He is currently the Principal Investigator of the Rural Technology Action Group at IIT Bombay. He is also heading the GTWG-ACT Project at IIT Bombay. Prof. Rao has several publications to his credit. One of his papers has been cited more than 1200 times on Google Scholar.


        </item>
        <item>
            Dr. Dipankar Chatterjee is a Senior Scientist at the CSIR-Central Mechanical Engineering Research Institute, Durgapur. Dr. Chatterjee holds a PhD degree from IIT Kharagpur. He has previously served at LPMI, Arts et Métiers Paris Tech, France (as Post Doctoral Fellow) and at the Indian School of Mines (as Assistant Professor). Dr. Chatterjee specializes in Computational modeling of fluid flow, heat transfer and species transport. He has authored 64 SCI publications, one book and two chapters in books. He has completed a major RandD Project funded by DST and is Project Leader of Project CoalGasUrja from CSIR-CMERI. He is Associate Editor of two international journals and also serves on the Editorial Boards of two journals. He is guiding several PhD and Masters dissertations. He also headed the Simulation and Modeling Laboratory at CSIR-CMERI for four years.

        </item>
        <item>

Ajay Kumar Singh is a senior scientist at the CSIR-Central Institute of Mining and Fuel Research (serving since 1988), Dhanbad, India. He headed the Methane Emission and Degasification Division at CSIR-CIMFR for a period of almost two decades, during which he initiated a number of new research areas within the department.

\nDr. Singh has led numerous projects as Project Leader/Coordinator on diverse areas such as estimation of fugitive methane estimation from coal mines in India, coalbed methane potentiality studies, underground coal gasification and carbon sequestration. He is the key person to determine the national methane emission factor for coal mining and handling activities in India and also to prepare the estimates of fugitive emission to the atmosphere from India100s coal and oil and natural gas systems on behalf of the Ministry of Environment and Forests, Government of India as a part of India100s National Communication to the United Nations Framework Convention on Climate Change. Some of the major project he has performed have been funded by UNDP, US EPA, Ministry of Coal, Department of Electronics and Information Technology, GSI, CIL, ONGC, BHEL and several other government and industrial agencies. Currently, he is heading the CSIR Network Project on Underground Coal Gasification (Project CoalGasUrja).

\nDr. Singh has been a lead author in the 2006 IPCC Guidelines on National Greenhouse Gas Inventories. For his contribution to the IPCC, he received honorary citations from the Hon100ble Prime Minister of India as well as the Chairman of the IPCC. He also authored a background report on Underground Coal Gasification under the aegis of TIFAC, DST.

\nDr. Singh has more than 50 papers in journals and conference proceedings, apart from 150+ technical reports. He has also served as reviewer for several international journals and conferences. He has guided and is currently guiding several doctoral and masters students.

\nHe obtained his PhD degree from IIT Kanpur in 1991.


        </item>
        <item>
            
Dr. Debadutta Mohanty is a Senior Scientist at the CSIR-Central Institute of Mining and Fuel Research. He holds a PhD degree in Geology from IIT Roorkee. He has more than thirty publications in peer-reviewed journals and conference proceedings. He has also held visiting positions at the Southern Illinois University at Carbondale, Ergo Exergy Inc and The University of Queensland. He is a fellow of the Geological Society of India. As part of a SERB funded project, he designed and developed indigenously a unique high pressure adsorption isotherm experimental setup at CSIR-CIMFR for research on unconventional gas reservoir systems and CO2- sequestration under replicated in situ conditions.

        </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="eventtime">
        <item>09:00-10:00</item>
        <item>10:00-10:30</item>
        <item>10:30-11:45</item>
        <item>11:45-13:00</item>
        <item>13:00-14:00</item>
        <item>14:00-15:15</item>
        <item>15:15-16:30</item>
        <item>16:30-16:45</item>
        <item>16:45-18:00</item>


    </string-array>
    <string-array name="eventname">
        <item>Joint Inaugural Session of UCG-2017 and EMT-2017</item>
        <item>HIGH TEA</item>
        <item>Role of clean coal technology
in India’s energy security</item>
        <item>Underground Coal
Gasification: A Synoptic
View</item>
        <item>LUNCH</item>
        <item>Global Development of
Commercial Underground
Coal Gasification</item>
        <item>Mathematical Modelling of
Coal Gasification Processes</item>
        <item>TEA BREAK</item>
        <item>Some modelling and
experimental studies on UCG
in India</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="eventspeaker">

        <item>Dr. P K Singh, Chair,
            \nUCG-2017
            Organizing Secretaries</item>
        <item> zz </item>
        <item>Prof. Amit Garg\n
IIM Ahmedabad</item>
        <item>Dr. Ajay K Singh
\nCSIR-CIMFR, Dhanbad</item>
        <item>zz</item>
        <item>Dr. Michael S Blinderman
\nErgo Exergy Inc., Canada</item>
        <item>Prof T Sundararajan
\nIIT Madras</item>
        <item>zz</item>
        <item>Prof. Sanjay M Mahajani
\nIIT Bombay</item>

    </string-array>


</resources>
